{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Oil, Fuel or Water Tank Removal Services","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40434/":{"taskOID":40434,"originalTaskOID":40434,"setID":725,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":4813,"questionDisplayText":"Kind of Tank","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of tank needs to be removed? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":589,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Above ground","answerDisplayText":"Above ground","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1016,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Below ground","answerDisplayText":"Below ground","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6069,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Steel","answerDisplayText":"Steel","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2427,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Fiberglass","answerDisplayText":"Fiberglass","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4770,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Polyethylene (plastic)","answerDisplayText":"Polyethylene (plastic)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":750,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Aluminum","answerDisplayText":"Aluminum","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4814,"questionDisplayText":"Material Stored in Tank","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What was stored in the tank?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":2763,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Gasoline","answerDisplayText":"Gasoline","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1912,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Diesel","answerDisplayText":"Diesel","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2962,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Heating oil","answerDisplayText":"Heating oil","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6842,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Water","answerDisplayText":"Water","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1364,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Chemical","answerDisplayText":"Chemical","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4816,"questionDisplayText":"How Long Since Tank Was Used","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"How long since the tank has been used?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":3166,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"In use now, needs replacing","answerDisplayText":"In use now, needs replacing","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3165,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"In use now, needs removing","answerDisplayText":"In use now, needs removing","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":294,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1-3 years","answerDisplayText":"1-3 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":455,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"3-5 years","answerDisplayText":"3-5 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":542,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"6-10 years","answerDisplayText":"6-10 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":315,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"10+ years","answerDisplayText":"10+ years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4817,"questionDisplayText":"Leakage Details","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Is there evidence of leaking?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7194,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Yes, unexplained iincrease in oil usage","answerDisplayText":"Yes, unexplained iincrease in oil usage","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7178,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Yes, large amounts of water in tank","answerDisplayText":"Yes, large amounts of water in tank","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7180,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Yes, loss of product during off-season","answerDisplayText":"Yes, loss of product during off-season","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7189,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Yes, oil odors in drinking water","answerDisplayText":"Yes, oil odors in drinking water","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7188,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Yes, oil odors around oil burner","answerDisplayText":"Yes, oil odors around oil burner","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7181,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Yes, loss of vegetation in area over tank","answerDisplayText":"Yes, loss of vegetation in area over tank","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":4813,"questionDisplayText":"Kind of Tank","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of tank needs to be removed? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":589,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Above ground","answerDisplayText":"Above ground","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1016,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Below ground","answerDisplayText":"Below ground","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6069,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Steel","answerDisplayText":"Steel","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2427,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Fiberglass","answerDisplayText":"Fiberglass","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4770,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Polyethylene (plastic)","answerDisplayText":"Polyethylene (plastic)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":750,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Aluminum","answerDisplayText":"Aluminum","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":589,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Above ground","answerDisplayText":"Above ground","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1016,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Below ground","answerDisplayText":"Below ground","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6069,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Steel","answerDisplayText":"Steel","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2427,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Fiberglass","answerDisplayText":"Fiberglass","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4770,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Polyethylene (plastic)","answerDisplayText":"Polyethylene (plastic)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":750,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Aluminum","answerDisplayText":"Aluminum","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4814,"questionDisplayText":"Material Stored in Tank","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What was stored in the tank?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":2763,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Gasoline","answerDisplayText":"Gasoline","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1912,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Diesel","answerDisplayText":"Diesel","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2962,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Heating oil","answerDisplayText":"Heating oil","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6842,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Water","answerDisplayText":"Water","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1364,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Chemical","answerDisplayText":"Chemical","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":2763,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Gasoline","answerDisplayText":"Gasoline","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1912,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Diesel","answerDisplayText":"Diesel","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2962,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Heating oil","answerDisplayText":"Heating oil","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6842,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Water","answerDisplayText":"Water","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1364,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Chemical","answerDisplayText":"Chemical","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4816,"questionDisplayText":"How Long Since Tank Was Used","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"How long since the tank has been used?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":3166,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"In use now, needs replacing","answerDisplayText":"In use now, needs replacing","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3165,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"In use now, needs removing","answerDisplayText":"In use now, needs removing","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":294,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1-3 years","answerDisplayText":"1-3 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":455,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"3-5 years","answerDisplayText":"3-5 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":542,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"6-10 years","answerDisplayText":"6-10 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":315,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"10+ years","answerDisplayText":"10+ years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":3166,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"In use now, needs replacing","answerDisplayText":"In use now, needs replacing","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3165,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"In use now, needs removing","answerDisplayText":"In use now, needs removing","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":294,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1-3 years","answerDisplayText":"1-3 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":455,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"3-5 years","answerDisplayText":"3-5 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":542,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"6-10 years","answerDisplayText":"6-10 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":315,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"10+ years","answerDisplayText":"10+ years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4817,"questionDisplayText":"Leakage Details","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Is there evidence of leaking?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7194,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Yes, unexplained iincrease in oil usage","answerDisplayText":"Yes, unexplained iincrease in oil usage","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7178,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Yes, large amounts of water in tank","answerDisplayText":"Yes, large amounts of water in tank","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7180,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Yes, loss of product during off-season","answerDisplayText":"Yes, loss of product during off-season","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7189,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Yes, oil odors in drinking water","answerDisplayText":"Yes, oil odors in drinking water","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7188,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Yes, oil odors around oil burner","answerDisplayText":"Yes, oil odors around oil burner","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7181,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Yes, loss of vegetation in area over tank","answerDisplayText":"Yes, loss of vegetation in area over tank","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7194,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Yes, unexplained iincrease in oil usage","answerDisplayText":"Yes, unexplained iincrease in oil usage","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7178,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Yes, large amounts of water in tank","answerDisplayText":"Yes, large amounts of water in tank","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7180,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Yes, loss of product during off-season","answerDisplayText":"Yes, loss of product during off-season","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7189,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Yes, oil odors in drinking water","answerDisplayText":"Yes, oil odors in drinking water","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7188,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Yes, oil odors around oil burner","answerDisplayText":"Yes, oil odors around oil burner","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7181,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Yes, loss of vegetation in area over tank","answerDisplayText":"Yes, loss of vegetation in area over tank","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true,"__cache./api/resource/task/40434/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40434,"taskName":"Water or Fuel Tank - Remove","taskDescription":"Remove a Water or Fuel Tank","xmTaskDescriptor":"Oil, Fuel or Water Tank Removal Services","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":1703,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"Fuel pressure move hot excavation","textMessagingName":"Remove Tank","rolloverLongDesc":"For fuel tanks, they are familiar with the appropriate environmental regulations.","rolloverShortDesc":"Includes above ground \u0026 buried tanks.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Remove a Water or Fuel Tank.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Oil, Fuel \u0026 Water Tank Removal \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":29,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":0,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Water or Fuel Tank Remove","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Water or Fuel Tank - Remove","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Water or Fuel Tank Project","urlName":"Water-or-Fuel-Tank-Remove","taskConsiderationId":1,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":false,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Oil, Fuel \u0026 Water Tank Removal Companies - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | HomeAdvisor Reviews, Costs","searchKeywords":"Fuel,pressure,move,hot,excavation,Storage,Tank,Removal,excavate,Water,Delivery","emcCategoryOid":-12028,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":725,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false}}